invitemedia.com 2011-12-25

# Invite Media - Next generation platform for display media trading

**Effective: September 1, 2011**

Invite Media (“we” or “us”), headquartered in the United States, is an online advertising and technology company. We provide this privacy policy so that we may inform you about how our technology (“Technology”), based on Bid Manager™, processes information on behalf of online advertisers, website owners and other businesses that use our services (our “Clients”). This policy also outlines our privacy practices on our corporate Website (“Website”), www.invitemedia.com. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@invitemedia.com](mailto:privacy@invitemedia.com). ****

**Privacy Practices for our Technology**

**WHAT DOES INVITE MEDIA DO?**  
****  
Invite Media runs a platform that allows our clients to buy or sell ad space on websites for online advertising. Our clients are businesses engaged in Internet advertising - advertisers, publishers, ad networks or ad agencies. Our clients buy and sell media by participating in online exchanges for ad space. Our Bid Manager technology powers this platform. When ad space on a website is bought or sold, usually to an advertiser, ad agency or ad network by a publisher, the Bid Manager technology, as an agent for its clients, fulfills the transaction by delivering the ad to the Internet user who visits that site. Generally, an Internet user's computer comes into contact with Invite Media when a user visits a website, or views an ad, powered by the Bid Manager technology. The ads sent by the Bid Manager technology are sent from the domain invitemedia.com, sometimes through client domains that forward ads and ad requests to and from invitemedia.com.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION OUR TECHNOLOGY COLLECTS**

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
****  
We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) via our Technology. PII is only collected on this website (www.invitemedia.com) in the Jobs section if you were to submit a resume to Invite Media for recruiting purposes.Click here to read that section of our privacy policy.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
****  
We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) via our Technology, including but not limited to your IP host address, the date and time of the ad request, pages viewed, browser type, the referring URL, Internet Service Provider, and your computer's operating system. Customers of our Technology may utlize non-PII data that is delivered by third party providers from online or offline sources.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
****  
Our technology uses cookies in conjunction with Web beacons in order to help make the online advertisements you see more relevant to you. We also use cookies and web beacons so that we can measure the success of our online advertising campaigns, and the campaigns of our Clients.

**What are cookies?**  
****  
Cookies are small text files that web servers typically send to users’ computer when they visit a website. Cookies are stored as text files on users’ hard drive, and can be accessed by web servers when the user returns to a website or goes to another website. Cookies are used by companies to collect and send information about a user’s website visit – for example, number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, navigation history through the website, and other statistics. This information helps companies improve a user’s online experience in many ways: for example, by allowing companies to monitor website performance, make the website easier to use, measure the effectiveness of their promotional placements, and tailor their website to better match a user’s interests and preferences. _Cookies cannot be used to access any other data on a user’s hard drive, or to personally identify them._ Users who prefer not to accept cookies can set their Internet browser to notify them when they receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being placed on their hard drive. 

****HOW IS OUR INFORMATION SECURED AND PROTECTED?**  
****  
** All of the user data collected by Invite Media is stored only in anonymous form, meaning that information about a specific user cannot be retrieved. Even so, we maintain physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect all our data from accidental, unauthorized or unlawful access, use, modification, disclosure, loss, or destruction. The data is kept on a secure server and we restrict access to the data solely to authorized users. No security measures, however thorough, are perfect and there can be no absolute assurance of security and therefore, we cannot and do not offer an absolute guarantee or warrant the security of the information we possess. **

**INFORMATION STORAGE AND SECURITY**

**

**Storage of Non-PII  
****  
** We retain the Non-PII collected via our Technology for up to 180 days in order to ensure that our Technology is functioning properly. After 180 days, we render this information anonymous and store it for up to three years.

**Information Security  
****  
** The security of your information is important to us. We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to the use of encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at [privacy@invitemedia.com](mailto:privacy@invitemedia.com). **

INFORMATION SHARING

**   
****  
The security of your information is important to us, including but not limited to the PII collected via the Website. We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to the use of firewalls and encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at[privacy@invitemedia.com](mailto:privacy@invitemedia.com).

As described above, Invite Media stores only aggregated data on its servers. We may share such aggregate, non-personal information with Publishers and Networks in connection with reporting and accounting needs as well as with other unaffiliated third parties for various purposes such as statistical or educational analysis.

We may disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

Also, in the event Invite Media is merged into another company, or another company acquires all or substantially all of Invite Media’s assets, including, without limitation, in the event of bankruptcy, all data compiled or owned by Invite Media may be among the items transferred in that transaction. In such event, all the data will continue to be governed by this Policy. 

**CONTROLLING THE USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Invite Media adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising, [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Opt-out from our cookies**  
****  
If you’d like to opt-out from having Invite Media collect your Non-PII in connection with our Technology, please click[here](http://assets.invitemedia.com/opt-out.html). When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your Non-PII to tailor our online advertisement campaigns. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

If you would like to opt-out using the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Deleting your PII**  
****  
Although we don’t collect PII via our Technology, if you'd like us to update, correct, delete or deactivate any PII that you have provided to us on the Website, please send your request to us at[privacy@invitemedia.com](mailto:privacy@invitemedia.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. 

**CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE**  
****  
The services of Invite Media are not intended for persons under 13 years of age. Invite Media’s products and services are not developed or directed at children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly market our products or services to children under the age of 13.

**CHANGES TO OUR POLICY**  
****  
We may revise this Policy at any time. Any changes and/or updates to the Policy will be updated directly on this page. We encourage you to visit this page periodically to review our current Policy so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information. In the event we make any material changes to this Policy we will advise our Publishers and Networks of such changes in advance.

**CONTACTING US**  
****  
Should you have any questions in regards to this Policy or Invite Media’s privacy practices, please contact our representatives at the following email and they will be more than happy to clarify and assist you in any way possible:[privacy@invitemedia.com](mailto:privacy@invitemedia.com), 866.422.0567, or by mail at: 

Google  
ATTN: Invite Media, Inc.  
76 9th Avenue, 4th Floor  
New York, NY 10011 

**Privacy Practices for our Website** **

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  

**Invite Media collects personally identifiable information (PII) in the Jobs section, such as personal name, company name and e-mail address. The information that Invite Media servers records is for reply only and is later on erased with no further use. Invite Media does not match any of the cookies-based data with other data in an attempt to identify a user and thus we will NEVER KNOW the identity of a user. If for any reason a user wishes to update/correcting their PII in the contact us section, please resubmit your contact information or send email to [info@invitemedia.com](mailto:info@invitemedia.com). ******NON-PERSONALLY IDENFTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
****  
We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) from visitors to this Website. Non-PII is information that cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to this Website, the referring URL and your computer's operating system.

**COOKIES**  
****  
We use persistent “cookies” on this Website in order to help us manage the opt-out process for our technology. For information on our opt-out process, please review the section of this privacy policy entitled “Opting out from Cookies” below. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. For more information about cookies please visit<http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>. No PII is collected by or associated with cookies from this Website. 

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**  
****  
The Invite Media website may contain links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy practices may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate only with reputable entities, Invite Media cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of all websites that you visit.

**UPDATING / DELETING YOUR PII**  
****  
If you’d like us to update, correct, delete, or deactivate any PII that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us at[privacy@invitemedia.com](mailto:privacy@invitemedia.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. 

| 

76 9th Avenue  
4th Floor (Google)  
New York, NY 10013
